jackboxgames.com 2019-10-22

# Privacy Policy - Jackbox Games

_Revised: January 26, 2018_

Jackbox Games is serious about protecting the privacy of its users. This Privacy Policy sets forth how Jackbox Games, Inc., its related companies and affiliates (collectively, “JBG,” “we,” or “us”) will collect, use and share information in connection with its products, services, and websites accessed through internet-capable hardware platforms including gaming consoles, personal computers, mobile devices, or in-game applications or software platforms including third-party hosts (collectively, the “Services”).

Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully. By using or registering for the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service and consent to our collection, use and sharing of your information as described below. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the Services, and does not apply to information that may be collected by us offline

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was revised. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

 **1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect “Personal Information” in a number of ways when you visit or use the Service. Personal Information is generally defined as information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, home address and telephone number. Additionally, we may also collect demographic information, such as your age, gender, country and zip code of residence, other geo-locational information, recent game purchases, and game ownership and preferences. This demographic information may be associated with your Personal Information. If this demographic information is connected with Personal Information, we will treat the demographic information as Personal Information. Personal Information does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the characteristics and activities of users of the Service, from which any Personal Information has been removed.

 **(a) Information You Give Us Directly  
** When you interact with the Service, we may collect, store, and use information that you voluntarily provide to us. For example, wnen you register with the Service or create an account with us, you may be required to provide certain identifying information, such as your name, address, age, e-mail address, a password and other information that helps us confirm that it is you accessing your account. In addition, you may voluntarily submit Personal Information when you make a purchase, sign up for newsletters, send us feedback, post on our Facebook fan page or submit  User Generated Content (as defined in our Terms of Service). We may also offer you the ability to import your address book contacts or manually enter e-mail addresses so that you can locate your contacts on the Service and invite those contacts to join you on the Service.

 **(b) Information About You Received From a Third Party  
** When you use or interact with the Service through a social network (e.g., Facebook) or other third party platform, game console, app, or service (“Third Party Service”), you are authorizing JBG to collect, store, and use, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any and all information that you agreed the Third Party Service could provide to JBG based on your privacy settings with the Third Party Service. This information may include Personal Information, such as, your name, user ID, profile picture, and user IDs of your friends. We may also obtain Personal Information about you from other sources, such as, our vendors, partners, and network advertising companies, and combine that information with information we have collected from or about you.

 **(c) Information Collected From Using the jackbox.tv Controller**  
Many of our games allow users to interact with the game or Service through the use of a web-based controller page which is accessed by visiting the jackbox.tv URL (or another customized URL that redirects to jackbox.tv) on the user’s personal computing device (the “Controller Website”). Users may be asked to provide Personal Information, such as their name, email and phone number, to access and use the Service via the Controller Website. JBG may also use cookies, pixels and other tracking technologies on the Controller Website from which it may collect additional usage information. In some cases, JBG may share information collected from the Controller Website, including Personal Information, with its partner companies. For example, JBG may partner with a company to provide a custom or co-branded version of a JBG game where users are required to provide certain Personal Information on the Controller Website. JBG may collect and share that information with its partner company so that they may contact users for their own marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications, you should contact the partner company with your request.

 **(d) Information About Your Play and Interaction With Other Players  
** We may collect information about how you use the Service and interact with other users of the Service, including on the Controller Website, to analyze user behavior in our games. For example, we may collect user information to determine a user’s average score, how often a user plays a particular game, activates certain features of the game, purchases premium content, and other Service-related events.

We may also collect, store, and use information that you provide through the social networking features available through the Service. Please note that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information on bulletin boards or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other internet users. We do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

 **(e) Payment Information  
** We may use third parties to manage the purchase of software, merchandise, virtual currency, or virtual items offered by the Service. In that case, we do not have access to (and thus do not collect or store) your credit card details or billing information. You acknowledge and agree that JBG will have no liability for or control over such third party company’s use or protection of your payment information. You should check the privacy policy of the independent third party company’s website to determine how it will handle any payment information it collects from you and/or processes. Please note, however, that we may collect, store, and use non-payment information relating to your purchase history, such as the products you have purchased and the frequency of those purchases.

 **(f) Technical Usage Information and Cookies  
** Log Data and Mobile Devices. When you use the Service, our servers record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Service, pages of the websites involved in the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for, access times and dates, and other information. If you access the Service from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device, such as your device type, geo-location, and operating system. Log Data is tied to your Personal Information in certain circumstances, such as if you have linked a Third Party Service account to your JBG account.

Cookies and Local Storage. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies (including but not limited to browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe flash technology), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your usage of Service, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen. Information contained in a cookie may also be linked to your Personal Information for purposes such as improving the quality of the Service, tailoring recommendations and ads to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although, if you do so, you may not be able to access or use the Service or certain of its features.

 **(g) Customer Support Information  
** When you ask for assistance from our customer support team, we will collect and store the contact information you provide (generally your name and e-mail address), information about your game play or activity on the Service, and your user ID number. We will also store and use the correspondence and any information contained within.

 **2\. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

JBG does not share your Personal Information with third parties except as approved by you or as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **(a) To Provide, Manage, and Promote the Service  
** We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the Service to you, including to analyze and improve the Service; to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising, and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on the Service, participate in contests, and promotions; to enable you to communicate and share with other users or services; and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries.

We may combine Personal Information with other information and use this combination in an effort to improve your experience or to aggregate it with information collected from other users to improve or analyze our Service. This privacy policy in no way limits or restricts our collection and dissemination of aggregate information, User Generated Content (as defined in the Terms of Service), or of non-personal information.

 **(b) To Allow Third-Parties to Assist Us In Providing and Managing the Service  
** We may share information, including Personal Information, with certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents, or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Service by, for example: developing or supporting products and features; conducting email marketing on our behalf; web-hosting; processing payments; administering message boards; fulfilling orders; processing data or statistics; or assisting with the administration, judging, and prize fulfillment aspects of contests and promotions. These outside service providers are required to protect any Personal Information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific services they are providing to JBG.

 **(c) To Facilitate Communication Between Friends and Other Players  
** If you access the Service through a Third Party Service, your friends on the Third Party Service may see your name, profile, and descriptions of your game activity (e.g., high scores and achievements). This information may also be used to provide in-game leader boards and promote in-game player achievements to you and other players. In addition, friends and other players will be able to see your game profile, which may include your name or a “game name” and your player likeness, profile photo, or other avatar representing you, which in certain cases can reveal your Third Party Service user ID. Access to your Third Party Service user ID may allow others to view the public information associated with your related Third Party Service account. Other players may also be able to send you game requests or even friend requests through the related Third Party Service’s communication channels.

 **(d) To Contact You  
** We are committed to providing you with the best possible user experience and, therefore, one of the key uses of your Personal Information is to communicate with you. We may periodically contact you in connection with customer support inquiries, to alert you as to the status of your account, and to keep you informed of your in-game activity, including comments from friends and notifications about in-game status, achievements, and standings. Some messages, such as invites for friends to join you in a game, may include your name and profile photo. We may also contact you by e-mail for research purposes so that we can continually improve and update the Service based on your input.

We may also send you communications directly or in partnership with companies other than JBG to provide you with special offers and other services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from JBG or its partners, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each party’s e-mail. There are certain service notification e-mails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are registered with or subscribed to the Service, such as notifications of changes to our Service or policies.

 **(e) To Deliver Relevant Advertising  
** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Service through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you use the Service. JBG works with various third-party advertising agents that use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect information. We do not share your Personal Information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the Service.

 **(f) To Others  
** We do not disclose your Personal Information to any third parties except as stated in this Privacy Policy, as otherwise permitted by law, or as authorized by you.  Where you opt in to permit your Personal Information to be shared with a third party, such third party may provide you with marketing and promotional offers that may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving communications directly from such third party, you can follow the opt out instructions in the emails that they send you

 **(g) Legal Matters; Safety  
** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information in situations that we believe to be emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat.

 **(h) Sale or Transfer of Assets  
** If JBG sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, JBG may transfer your Personal Information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

 **3\. POLICY REGARDING CHILDREN**

As set forth in our Terms of Service Agreement, the Service is not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 years of age. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will take commercially reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records. Parents should contact JBG immediately if they have any concerns. Please see the Contacting Us section below for further details.

 **4\. USER CONTROL AND RETENTION OF DATA**

If you have created an account with us (not through a Third Party Service), you may access and change your account information by visiting your account page and making the desired changes. To manage the information we receive about you from a Third Party Service, you will need to follow the instructions at that site for updating your information and changing your privacy settings. Once we receive your information from a Third Party Service, that information is stored and used by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you created an account with us directly (not through a Third Party Service), you may cancel the Service and close your account at any time. If you access the Service through a Third Party Service, you may cancel the Service by removing the relevant Service application (such as The JBG Party Pack on Steam) from your Third Party Service account. Please note that even after you cancel the Service, copies of some information that is publicly viewable may remain viewable in circumstances where, for example, your information has been posted on leader boards, you have commented on content on the Service or if another person copied, stored, or shared your information. As a matter of clarity, deactivation of an account is not immediate.

If you deactivate your account or remove the Service, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical, gameplay, and recordkeeping purposes and integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Service or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Service. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies.

 **5\. SECURITY**

We have put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. However, we do not guarantee, and explicitly disclaim any implied representation, warranty, or other promise, that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes. Also please note that e-mail and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us Personal Information through these mediums.

 **6\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites, online properties, or systems to which our Service may link or through which our Service may be accessed, and you accept that JBG is not responsible for the security or privacy practices of any such third party websites, properties or systems. In some instances, we may direct you to a site that is operated by a vendor or partner. Even though the page where you provide information may have the look and feel of the Service, a different privacy policy may govern that information collection by our vendor or partner.

 **7\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with us may choose to opt out of the disclosure of personal information about them to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. As stated above, our policy is not to disclose personal information collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you choose to opt-out at any time after granting approval, email support.

 **8\. INTERNATIONAL USERS**

If you are using the Service from outside the United States, by providing your information on the Service, you are consenting to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing, storage and maintenance in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service Agreement. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Service. We process and store your information in the United States and your information may be stored on servers located outside your residential jurisdiction and which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. If you access the Service from outside the United States, your usage of the Service constitutes consent to the transfer of your data outside of your country and to the United States.

 **9\. CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of the Service, please contact us at privacy@jackboxgames.com or write to us at:

Jackbox Games  
811 W. Evergreen Ave.  
Suite #301  
Chicago, IL 60642  
Attn: Customer Support
